Calculated fields create new fields from the underlying data,
“计算字段”(Calculated Fields) 从底层数据创建新字段
such as creating a revenue field by multiplying price times quantity.
例如创建一个用“价格”乘以“数量”得出的“收入”字段
Let's create a calculated field.
我们来创建计算字段
Maybe you want to know the profit,
或许你想知道
per item, for each quarter.
每个季度每项物品的利润
To create a calculated field,
要创建计算字段
open the menu on a field such as profit.
请打开一个字段上的菜单 如“利润”(Profit)
Then click, create calculated field.
点击“新建”(Create)-“计算字段”(Calculated Field)
You'll see the editor. On the left,
这时会出现编辑器
you can type in the formula you'd like to use to create the field.
在左边 你可以输入想要用于创建字段的公式
And, on the right, you'll see different formulas that you can choose from.
而在右边 你会看到可供选择的不同公式
Fields in the editor show up in brackets, like profit.
编辑器中的字段显示在方括号中 如 [profit]
You can do simple arithmetic here by adding a constant or multiplying by field.
你可以通过加上常量或乘以字段来进行简单的运算
You can also use functions such as absolute value,
你也可以使用
sine, square root, et cetera.
绝对值、正弦、平方根等函数
There is a list of functions on the right and
右侧有一个函数列表
some short documentation is shown when you select one.
当你选中某个函数时 会显示一些简短的文档
Here, we want to create a new field that calculates the profit,
在这里 我们要创建一个新的字段
per item, for each record.
用以计算每个记录每项物品的利润
It's pretty simple, just profit divided by quantity.
非常简单 用利润除以数量即可
You can name the calculated field here and I'll name it, profit per item.
你可以在此命名“计算字段” 我将它命名为 "Profit per Item"
Once you hit OK and create it,
在点击 OK 并创建它后
a new field shows up in the data pane.
数据窗格中便会显示一个新的字段
You can use it like any other field.
你可以像使用任何其他字段一样使用它
For example, I can make a plot of the average profit per item for each subcategory.
例如 绘制每个子类别每项物品的平均利润图
You can see where profit per item shows up in the data pane.
你看在数据窗格中 "Profit per Item" 字段显示的位置
And next to the number symbol is a little equal sign.
数字符号#旁边是一个小的等号
This indicates that it's a calculated field.
这表示它是一个计算字段
Going back to our original question,
回到我们原来的问题
we wanted to know the average profit per item.
我们想知道每项的平均利润
To change from sum to average,
要把总和变为平均值
we click the dropdown,
点击下拉菜单
go down to measure, change it to average.
找到“度量”(Measure) 将它更改为“平均值”(Average)
Here you see that profit for copiers is the highest and is lowest for tables.
在这里 你可以看到复印机的利润是最高的 而桌子的利润最低